Vod2smi by Blue-Bird™
That's them in there
just like that?
Just like that.
I wouldn't go in there
for a day or two.
Heard the expression
kick the hornet's nest?
I'll stay right
here. Thank you.
Those things scare me to death.
They been killing my honey bees.
A few days unchecked,
they'll wipe out
the whole colony.
What are you gonna do with them?
Well, that's
between me and them,
if you don't mind.
That's okay.
I understand these things.
I just wanted to thank you
for putting up with me,
and all of my bees.
This place was
crabgrass and weeds,
and you brought it back to life.
You're a blessing.
No one's ever taken
care of me before.
I'll, uh...
Mr. Clay...
Come back at suppertime.
Let me feed you.
Boss.
- You got something, yeah?
- I got one.
I want it. I need it.
Hey, put it in my ear.
Get this fucking hippie
shit down, please.
United Data Group. Good
afternoon. This is Boyd.
How may I help you?
Boyd.
Uh, hello. I just
got a message saying
that there's a problem
with my computer.
Don't you worry. The
message you received
is from our United Data
Group antivirus software.
It's part of the
software package
that you pre-installed
on your computer.
I'm sorry. I'm not
a computer person.
What did you say the name
of your product is again?
Now, our records show
that you actually
have an older version
on your account.
So what I'm going to need
you to do is uninstall that
and install the latest version.
Well, I have no
idea how to do that.
My daughter set up
everything for me.
Well, I would recommend
you take your computer
to an IT specialist.
However, keep in mind
that you will lose
all your data,
since they'll have to
replace the hard drive.
I'm pretty remote out here.
Everything I have
is on the computer.
Okay. There is actually
a software package
that you can download
that would allow me
to reinstall remotely.
All right. Tell me what to do.
It's okay. Can you,
uh, can you type this,
Friendly friend dot net?
Spelled just how it sounds.
Okay. I'm there.
And there should be a button
on your screen that
says "install."
Can you click on that button?
I clicked the button.
So you're about to
see some windows
open, close on your desktop,
as I reinstall the
virus shield for you.
Okay.
I hope you fucking clowns
are paying attention.
You stick to the script,
but not so much that you
sound like a goddamn robot.
All right?
She has got 10K checking,
life insurance
annuity, Roth IRA,
teacher's pension and...
Holy fucking shit!
All right.
She is a signatory
on a $2 million dollar account.
Some, uh... It's
some fucking charity.
All right, kids, let
the strip mining begin.
Ooh. My computer's
going crazy.
Totally normal.
Just do not touch your keyboard.
Because of this inconvenience,
I'm going to credit back
your subscription fees.
How about that?
I've gone ahead
and deposited $500
into the account ending 020.
Oh, that's not my account.
That's an account that I manage.
Can you log into that account
and verify the transfer,
please, Miss Parker?
Just hold on.
Yes, there's...
There's a transfer for $50,000?
Set the hook with sympathy.
Miss Parker, I...
I made a terrible mistake.
I was supposed to
credit you 500,
but I don't know, I
got a stuck key here.
I'm gonna lose my job here.
I got kids.
I ain't got fucking kids.
Oh, I don't want you to
get in trouble, but...
I could wire the amount back.
I will need a different
password though.
One second.
This is the master password
for all her accounts.
Okay, so the second we get
it, we zero out everything.
Um...
You know, I, um...
I think I should
call the bank. Hm?
You know what? You're
probably right.
But there goes my job,
and there goes all your data.
All my kids' pictures
are on this computer.
Okay.
Boom! Fucking yes!
That is what I am
talking about! Come on!
Let me fucking hear it! I
fucking love you people!
I fucking love you!
Hello?
Hello? You still there?
Uh-oh.
Oh.
What did I do?
Stupid...
Mrs. Parker?
Don't move.
Don't you fucking move.
Drop the knife.
Hands behind your back.
Slowly get on your knees
one knee at a time.
Now, who the fuck are you...
and what are you doing
in my mother's house?
Verona...
I'm so sorry.
How do you know my...
Mom.
Until we can clear him,
he's our best and only perp.
Clear him?
Agent Parker, I know
that's your mother.
I understand.
But there's a world where
she committed suicide.
Suicide? You can't be serious.
That woman loved life
more than anybody I know.
But by all means, let's
just completely ignore
the big white dude in
her house with a knife.
Get him up.
Come on.
It's Clay, right?
Adam Clay?
I don't have much to say.
Mr. Clay, we just got
a couple of questions.
Like, what the
fuck were you doing
in my mother's house?
I was bringing her
a jar of honey.
A jar of honey.
Who the fuck are
you? Winnie-the-Pooh?
I keep bees.
How do you know my mother?
I rent some space in
the barn from her.
I have a signed lease.
But what the fuck were
you doing in her house?
She didn't answer
when I knocked.
I noted her car in the driveway.
I heard the smoke
alarm and I entered.
You "noted"?
You got a law
enforcement background?
I told you, I take care of bees.
Oh, my God.
His hands tested negative
for gunshot residue.
But the prints on the
gun were your mother's.
It seems, sadly, it was suicide.
Mr. Clay, I need to
apologize for last night.
I realize I may have
been a little aggressive.
That's understandable.
Could I interest you in
something a bit stronger?
No.
But I'll sit with
you if you like.
No, thank you.
I wanted to thank you
for taking care of my mom.
I tried to stay in her
life as much as I could.
Obviously, I could
have done a better job.
Being old can be a lonely thing.
Turn a certain age, you cease
to exist. Cease to matter.
Used to be a part of
life, of the family.
Part of the hive, I
guess you could say.
There's some British Isles
hiding in your accent.
I was born there.
I hated that she
was out here alone.
She wouldn't leave.
There's too many memories.
You know, I think I
know why she liked you.
You're just like my brother.
He was in MARSOC,
a Marine Raider.
He was killed a few
years ago kicking doors.
She loved him.
He'd mow the lawn
and you'd think
he invented fire.
You know, while I
graduated the FBI Academy
and she said,
"Oh, that's nice."
She got scammed.
Somebody emptied out
all her accounts,
her savings, her retirement.
Got every penny. Maxed
out all her cards.
She was an educator,
director of a charity for kids.
They got two million
out of that account.
You know who did it?
I talked to an agent in
our cyber-crimes office.
This crew's been
operating for two years
and we don't even have names.
And even if we did, good
luck building an indictment
that would stand up in court.
Some defense attorney
would just argue that
the elderly victim agreed
to wire a complete stranger
his entire life savings.
Taking from an elderly person
is as bad as stealing
from a child.
Maybe worse.
Someone hurts a child,
there are parents.
People who care,
ready to step in.
Someone hurts an older person...
sometimes they're left to
face the hornets alone.
Because either it
goes unnoticed...
or no one cares.
I care.
And I'm stubborn.
And so help me God,
I'm going to get these
motherfuckers who did this.
I need to take care of the hive.
You've been up all night.
The hive is more important.
What are you doing?
- I thought you retired.
- I did.
I need a favor.
What kind of favor?
A name and address.
- Easy.
- Not easy.
Even the FBI can't
find these people.
Well, we're not the FBI, are we?
Shoot me the deets and stand by.
Yeah.
You weren't kidding.
This one kicked my butt.
They're routing
all over the world.
But you found them?
Sure. But who
are these people?
I'm gonna find out.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
The hell you think
you're going, pal?
This United Data Group?
Don't know nothing about that.
This is private property,
and you're trespassing.
I'm going inside.
I'm going to burn it down.
Yeah, that's not
happening, buddy.
You're not going
any-fucking-where
except right the fuck
back the way you came.
Do you know what they do here?
Buddy, I'm counting to three.
One, two, three.
There. I did it for you.
You aware this is
a criminal outfit?
Scamming the weakest
in our society.
Stealing everything they have.
Do you know that's
who you work for?
I'm looking for the call center.
Yeah, you're in the right place.
You just have to sign in here.
Tell any other companies
in the building
to evacuate now.
- There's going to be a fire.
- Okay. Th...
Thanks.
Hang up the phone.
Nah, I'm good, buddy. I'm
just doing my thing here.
Hang up the phone.
Uh, Miss Perkins, so
sorry, I'll have to
- call you right back.
- Everyone...
I need your attention, please.
Repeat after me.
I will never steal from the weak
and the vulnerable again.
I sent you a
department download,
and we'll find out
what's going on...
Repeat after me.
I will never steal from the weak
and the vulnerable again.
To help you keep that promise,
I'm gonna burn this
place to the ground.
Might be a good time to go home.
Oh, my God!
It's gas! MAN 4:
Fucking psycho.
It's gas!
It's gas! It's gas!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
What the fuck, bro?
What the fuck do you
think you're doing?
I'm a beekeeper.
I protect the hive.
Sometimes I use fire
to smoke out hornets.
This a multi-million
dollar operation, asshole.
Okay, so you can't come up here,
white-knighting shit.
Will you stomp his
ass out, please?
I got it. You fucking get him.
You fucking get him!
Bet you feel really
proud of yourself.
Mister...?
Uh...
- Uh, uh, Garnett.
- Mr. Garnett.
I don't care if your
friends here live or die.
The next call from your
little phishing scam
to this call center
will make a spark
across these wires.
Given all of the
gasoline fumes in here,
I promise you...
anything alive in here won't be.
Uh, guys, we might
want to dip out.
Hey. What's going on?
Uh, let me get flat white,
oat milk, of course,
and, uh, extra shot of espresso.
- Of course, sir.
- Thank you.
Good morning. Did we get
the otoro and the uni in?
- Yes, sure.
- We did?
- Yes.
- Fucking finally. Great.
- Hey, Michaela.
- Yes.
It... it came back.
The whole thing. Yeah.
And it's like I can
barely fucking move.
It's all tweaked.
- Oh, those are nice.
- Mmm-hmm.
- Those the new bowls?
- Yeah.
- That's perfect. Thank you.
- Mmm-hmm.
What? I'm in a meeting.
You said hit me on voice
if there's an emergency.
Okay. Right. Well, uh...
It seems we had a
disgruntled customer.
Uh, I just can't comprehend
why you're bothering me.
Just get in touch
with the attorney
and start shoving back.
Well, yeah, I don't think
that legal's gonna help much.
Okay, tell me what the
fuck is going on right now.
This dude just strolls in
saying we're
stealing from people,
and he just tears through
all my security guys,
like, fucking tissue
paper and, um...
And what?
And he burns the
place to the ground.
Yeah. The call center is gone.
I'm standing here staring
at a $30 million building,
it's now a giant
fucking ashtray.
Four people didn't get out.
You're telling me
that this asshole
burnt the entire building down
and dropped four fucking bodies?
Yeah, that's not exactly a
disgruntled customer, is it?
Who did this? Give
me a name right now.
Sir, I don't have it.
All the cameras and the
drives burned up in the fire.
He had a hat.
Oh, he had a hat. Okay.
I'm gonna hit you
back. All right?
I got to go big-dog
this shit for a minute.
- Hey, I need to talk to you.
- About what?
What? What? No, nothing.
I mean, if I had a friend
who, like, had a call center
and someone burned it down,
maybe killed some people,
you could get him, right?
Get him?
Yeah, like disappear
the problem.
Come on.
I'll be an hour.
That's way above my pay grade.
You literally ran the CIA,
and you're telling me
you can't just find
some guy in Massachusetts?
Listen, this sounds like
a job for the police.
I just need a name.
Well, you won't get it from me.
And you keep me a
million miles away
from your metaverse meth lab
or whatever it is.
Yup.
So check it out.
Daddy can't hold your
hand on this one.
Uh, this is clearly some
kind of crime of passion,
spur of the moment,
someone snapped, like, whatever.
But, uh, what we're
going to do is
I'm going to send
you some credentials,
you're going to
log into our cloud
and you're going to
look at anyone connected
to the last few deals
you closed. All right?
Just, I don't know, start there.
And, like, what if
I find this guy?
Then what?
You get a wrecking crew together
and you go Goodfellas on him.
I mean, come on, you're
a connected guy, right?
Do you understand?
Yeah. No, I
understand. I, uh...
I'll get it done.
It's called a day off.
V, you good?
Yeah, I'm great. Why?
I mean, you did lose
your mother yesterday.
Yeah.
What do you want, Wiley?
Are you leaving?
Please don't go.
I'm going to yoga.
Remember United Data Group?
Go on.
You sober enough to drive?
Yeah.
Give us a few
seconds, thank you.
Where's mine?
It's an old cup from my car
with instant and gas
station hot water.
Ew.
- You want a sip?
- No.
So the fire fried
all the CCTV footage.
Receptionist said she saw
some jacked dude in his 40s,
manhandled security
and walked in
with a couple gas cans.
This clown car saw everything,
but no one's talking.
They're all frequent
fliers with perjury,
fraud and cyber BeEFs.
Fucking scumbags. I
want IDs on all of them.
You know, this is just the tip
of, like, 20 spears, right?
Can I just have this moment?
Eloise Parker.
Yeah, I took her for over
two million yesterday.
She's, uh... she's Black,
widow, just has a
daughter in Boston.
I don't think this
is it, but, you know.
You said your boy has
an old-ass pickup truck.
That's him.
What the hell are those?
Fucking beehives.
Yeah, dickhead was
talking about them.
I guess he's a, like, bee lover.
You know what?
He breaks my shit,
you break his shit.
Where you at, bee boy?
You fucking hiding, bitch?
Come out and fucking face us!
Bye, bitch, now!
Let's go!
Shit, shit, shit, shit, shit!
Can someone, like,
fucking help me?
Fuck.
No! I'm okay.
We can talk about this.
Let's just work this out,
me and you. We can fix...
No, no!
Oh, fuck! Fuck! Fuck!
So, help me understand
because I'm a little confused.
What's the nature
of your business?
Don't know nothing
about no business.
So then why are
people just wiring you
their entire life savings?
Must be your
winning personality.
They got us lawyers,
so maybe you want
to talk to them.
You know, this is a really
nice shirt, by the way.
Did you steal it out of
a casket, you dog fucker?
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa. Uh...
Verona, if you're
done shitting all over
this gentleman's civil rights,
can I speak to you for a moment?
That's a nice shirt.
- V.
- Yeah, I know. I know.
I'm an asshole.
Oh, so you like fires?
Yeah, today I do.
Good, 'cause, uh,
today's your lucky day.
'Cause apparently,
your mother's house
is on fire, too,
and some other shit.
- Let's go.
- Wait. What?
Yeah. Shit's on
fire. Let's go.
You good?
V, you okay?
Yeah.
- That's a new one.
- Jesus Christ.
Where's Maggie?
Hey, Maggie, ID?
- United Data Group.
- Well, he's handsome.
Thank you.
Are you okay?
Yeah, Wiley, I'm
good. I'm good.
You think there's even
the remotest chance
that the dude who burned
down United Data Group
is the same guy
renting this spot
from your mother?
The beekeeper.
I lost my virginity
in that barn.
Fucking shit.
The universe is going
to have to wait.
I gotta take this.
Yo, what's up, playa?
This is the part
where you tell me
what a good job you did,
and I put you on a G6 to
Hawaii to chill for a week.
I'm so sorry, Mr. Danforth.
Did you fuck this up?
Are you fucking
crying right now?
I'm not crying. I'm bleeding.
Bleeding? Why
are you bleeding?
What do you mean, bleeding?
My fingers on my right hand.
He cut them off.
Okay. Fuck off. Go. Go.
He? Who the fuck is he?
Tell me who he is right now.
I don't know. A
fucking beekeeper.
Makes honey and
fucks with beehives.
He fucks with beehives?
What's he saying about bees?
I don't know. He
said he was, like,
protecting the
hive or something.
Oh, fuck, man. What the...
Oh, Jesus Christ!
No, no, no! Bro, bro, bro!
What do you want from me?
You want money? You
want crypto? NFTs?
I got fucking NFTs.
What are you fucking... What?
No! Dude, what the
fuck is this, man?
Don't move.
I fucking can't move!
You're fucking crazy, man.
What the fuck, bro?
What the fuck! No, no,
no, no! No, no, no!
Fucking stop the
fucking car! No! No!
Who do I have the
pleasure of speaking with?
Fuck you. That's who.
You burned down
my million-dollar
fucking call center.
Now I'm going to burn you down.
You haven't told me your name.
I told you my name.
It's fuck you. Mr. Fuck You.
You better fucking remember it.
Because you don't burn me down.
I burn you down.
You understand me?
You are fucking with forces
that you cannot comprehend.
You sound young.
I bet you don't have
estate planning.
I'm fucking 28 years old.
Why would I need that?
I'm about to show you.
Breaking news in Springfield,
where three bodies
have been discovered
following an arson
fire at a small farm.
There was an office
building explosion...
- And you say one guy did this?
- Yup.
Killed seven armed men
without firing a shot.
Yup. And he said he
was going to kill me.
And this is your
data mining consumer
service business, right?
Yes, something like that.
Pulling in 9 million
a month in one office.
I've got, like, 20.
Yeah.
And the only thing
you know about him
is he says he's a beekeeper.
Yeah, it's like his
whole brand or whatever.
Jesus.
What?
For someone who has elevated
fucking up into an art form,
this might well
be your 'Mona Lisa'.
How did I fuck up?
I don't know. You've
done something.
You've disturbed a Beekeeper.
Oh.
Oh, okay. So fucking what?
Why'd I care if
the guy keeps bees?
If a Beekeeper says
you're gonna die,
you're gonna die.
There's nothing I can do
or anybody else to stop it.
So, like, what do you
even do here, then?
What good are you?
Yeah.
I did 35 years of loyal
government service,
culminating as
director of the world's
premier intelligence agency.
I could have done anything,
but I chose this job as
a favor to your mother.
I keep Danforth
Enterprises safe.
Keep her reputation
safe, her name safe.
It's my fucking
name too, all right?
Oh, sit down.
I put up with you.
I've put up with your tantrums,
kept you out of the tabloids,
kept you out of jail.
The endless stream
of sex workers.
You're a drowning
man. Do you know that?
Mm.
You're scared.
Dead right I'm scared.
Terrified. So should you be.
Wallace, just tell me
what the fuck this guy is.
He's probably the
last pair of eyes
that you're going to sneer at.
Okay, listen.
Remember our favorite
burning building?
United Data Group.
The guys who work
there are hackers,
con men, fraudsters,
et cetera, et cetera.
Guy who ran it. Garnett.
He's in the book. He's
a known mob associate.
He's missing, but I've
got PD chasing him down.
Okay, so I had some
analysts run some shit,
and I think I'm starting to
get the shape of the animal.
Dude, I think United Data Group
is one of several call centers.
So there's got to be
like a central office
that's controlling all of them,
and that's what we got to find.
Wiley, this could be like
a billion-dollar-a-year
operation.
- Hello?
- Hey!
Did you hear a single
word I just said?
Yeah.
And?
I was just thinking
you come in here,
hungover on your day off,
and gain more
yardage on this thing
than the whole squad
has in two years.
Yeah, well, they
fucked with my family.
What'd you get on Clay?
- Your beekeeper?
- Yeah.
He's a ghost.
What?
Yeah, all I have is
a birth certificate
and a social.
The guy's never even -
had a bank account,
credit card, flown on a plane.
I ran his prints
through every database
I can think of, no hits.
That's bullshit.
This dude is former
military all day.
No hits. I'm telling you.
Either he's never been printed,
or Adam Clay doesn't exist.
Which is terrifying to me
because he's probably
in a classified program.
Special Agent Wiley.
Okay.
- Let's go.
- What?
- They found the guy, Garnett.
- They found him. Let's go.
- Oh, shit.
Jessica.
I think you know
why I'm calling.
You know, I'd do
anything for you.
Anything for you.
Derek's scared shitless.
I've never seen him this scared.
Well, he's made his bed.
I'll give you a board seat
on the holding company.
That's another million a year.
Plus you promised
you'd take care of him.
Look, I don't need
that. I have enough.
So you got this?
Yeah. You have my word.
Wallace...
I still think of you...
sometimes.
Sometimes.
Why are you calling me
on the "never call
this line" line?
This is priority one, Janet.
Well, if it was priority
one, I would know about it.
Look, I'm heading
downtown to a POTUS brief.
Just hear me out.
Now, you know who I
work for, don't you?
Oh, yeah. God
help you, Wallace.
Exactly.
Well, Director Harward,
my young friend,
seems to have caught
the unwanted attentions of...
I don't know how
else to say this.
Of a Beekeeper.
Wait, a Beekeeper Beekeeper?
As in.
- Well, that's not good.
- No, it's not.
- What's the body count?
- Seven today.
You busy making
funeral arrangements?
I need help, Janet. Not jokes.
Is that Garnett?
He was strapped
to an old pickup.
Check this out.
Does this mean you've
taken pity on an old man?
So your problem? He's
retired from the program.
No longer active.
Well, that changes everything.
The current active Beekeeper
is aware of the issue
and is going to be
taking things from here.
You can rest easy, old friend.
Oh, no. Janet.
The current active Beekeeper
is a fucking lunatic
who should have been
removed months ago.
God help us now.
Get out of here!
Shit!
- Excuse me.
- You're cool.
You've been a busy bee.
You're supposed to be retired.
I'm assuming you're
my replacement.
Fuck you!
I need your keys.
There's an issue.
The problem has not been solved.
Well...
That is a surprise.
The Beekeepers have
studied the situation
and have decided
to remain neutral.
How can they do that?
He was their man,
for fuck's sake!
I'm sorry, Wallace.
You're on your own.
I thought you could
fucking handle this.
I can handle this!
Thank you.
What you got for us, Detective?
That's her vehicle,
registered to a
Anisette Landress.
The ATF are en route
inbound to take care of it.
We're way cooler than ATF.
I'll show you why I called them.
That's a Minigun.
They use those on
military vehicles.
Did you know that puppy
shoots 6,000 rounds a minute?
I know.
Did you know that's
100 rounds a second?
Yep, I know.
Did you know that
you know a lot?
Yes, I do.
It's because I minored in math.
I'm a pretty smart guy actually.
Okay, then, do you know
who Anisette Landress is?
- Yes, I do.
- Go ahead and tell me.
Someone who doesn't exist
in any commercial or
government database.
Someone who's a ghost.
Like our good friend Adam Clay.
"Beekeeping for Beekeepers."
Here's another reason
that Anisette Landress
is like our good
friend Adam Clay.
Do you know what's that way?
Springfield...
where the call
center was torched.
And that way where
Adam Clay's headed?
Boston.
Let's go.
Thank you.
How are you, my friend?
- Good to see you, sir.
- Good to see you.
Yeah, come on,
leave them alone.
Leave them alone.
Don't play with those
things. They go off.
Sit down. Make
yourself comfortable.
When I was sworn in as director,
I was read into programs
I never imagined existed.
Well...
there are programs
even I wasn't privy to.
Like the Beekeepers.
The honeybee has always
had a special relationship
with humanity.
A sacred relationship.
Why? No bees, no agriculture.
No agriculture, no civilization.
Our nation is not
unlike a beehive,
with its complex
systems of workers,
caretakers, even royalty.
If any of the beehive's
complex mechanisms
are compromised,
the hive collapses.
Someone a long time ago decided
that a mechanism was needed
to keep our nation safe.
A mechanism outside
the chain of command,
outside the system.
Its one mission, to
keep the system safe.
Beekeepers are
given all resources,
empowered to act on
their own judgment.
For decades, they
have quietly worked
to keep the hive safe.
That is, until now.
It appears that a
retired Beekeeper
has gone off program
and is acting in what
he mistakenly believes
is the hive's best interest.
Can't somebody just
pick up the phone
and tell this yahoo to
stand-the-fuck down?
That's the one thing
Beekeepers don't do.
Stand down.
Not unlike bees themselves,
Beekeepers keep
working until they die.
So he's basically one of us.
No. He's not like you.
You're tier one operators,
former SEAL Team
Six, Delta Group.
You are, in other
words, pussies.
If you were in the same room,
he would kill you.
With enough of you, then
maybe you just might
in fact be able to kill him
before he accomplishes his goal.
What would that be?
To kill his way to
the top of the hive.
Mr. Pettis, you should
get your people moving.
Dude, bees are
interesting little shits.
Did you know that?
I know they pollinate
a bunch of shit
and we'd be fucked without them.
Listen.
"Some bees are queen slayers,
"which will rise up
and kill their queen
"if she fails to produce
"the right kind of
male offspring."
Fascinating.
- No.
- Hm. Nope.
- No!
- It's your turn. You can't...
Special Agent Parker.
Yeah.
Okay.
Thank you.
What?
The deputy director is
flying up from DC to see us.
Oh, fuck. This is your fault.
Here's another
interesting factoid.
Thank fuck.
You know, I was getting
sick of enjoying
my peaceful thoughts.
Sir.
Sir, this is Special
Agent Parker,
Special Agent Wiley.
They'll be briefing you.
This is Deputy Director Prigg
and Amanda Munoz,
special counsel.
Mr. Deputy Director,
my colleague and I believe
that three major crime
scenes in our area
are connected to
a single subject.
Adam Clay.
He killed six people today.
Based on the extensive
use of tradecraft
and the nature of his alias,
we believe that
Mr. Clay is connected
to a classified program
named Beekeeper.
A program that none of
our partner agencies
seem willing to acknowledge.
Let's stick to what we
know, Special Agent Parker.
Yes, sir.
In any event, this
individual is highly capable
and extremely motivated,
and we believe that he's
on his way to Boston,
if not already here.
And we believe that
this is his next target,
Nine Star United,
which appears to be the entity
operating the
regional call centers,
like the one that
Mr. Clay burned down.
Why is Adam Clay
on this rampage?
He's, um, protecting
the hive, sir.
It's what Beekeepers do.
I have enough to
brief the director.
- What's your ask?
- My ask?
Uh, well, a SWAT
team, for starters.
Surveillance support,
additional agents, analysts.
That shouldn't be a problem.
Thank you.
- Did that just happen?
- Yeah.
All right.
Everybody, listen up.
It's roll call time.
I'm getting ready for
my dick to get hard
with some wonderful,
beautiful numbers.
Let's start with
Phoenix. Where we at?
Phoenix is up 201K.
200K, I'm gonna suck
your dick. I love you.
New Orleans, show me,
tell me. Where we at?
It's down 93K, boss.
Down? You're a fucking loser.
You give me a fucking headache.
You give me fucking cancer.
New York, make me
happy. I beg you.
New York City's up 64 ASCOT.
Yeah! I love you, New York!
Gather around!
I want all weapons
front on entry.
- Everybody give me an oos!
- Oos!
Let's go!
Power down, my federal
friend. Power down.
Private security here on
the orders of the Governor.
State Department
certified to carry weapons
in all 50 states.
Feel free to call the
highlighted numbers
to verify.
You're not welcome
here. Get the fuck out.
All right, boys, let's go!
Set up a perimeter outside.
Your goals, they mean bonuses.
Money, money, money,
we fucking love it.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
What the fuck?
Who the fuck are you?
You can't be in here.
We're the guys
keeping you alive.
Shut it down now.
Everybody, listen up.
Anyone who's not
carrying a weapon,
get the fuck out!
Shouldn't you be killing
bin Laden or something?
Listen to me, my friend.
This place prints money.
No one's shutting down.
Anybody so much as puts a
phone down, they're fired!
I'm sorry to break it to you,
but bin Laden's been
dead for a while.
So I'm going to say
this one last time.
Shut it down.
The fuck I am.
Call your fucking boss.
You want me to call my boss?
I'll do that.
And you'll be so fucked,
it's gonna be beautiful.
Don't be shy. Come on.
What about the parking garage?
Closed and locked. Steel gate.
I want a body on
comms watching it.
- Delivery dock?
- Same deal.
- Station an agent there too.
- Yes, sir.
Sure there's no back
entrances into this place?
Hey, there're no
other entrances.
Federal law enforcement
operation in progress.
Move along at a minimum retreat
to a safe distance. Thank you.
Someone scout the
service tunnel.
The other option,
instead of going in
is to smoke them out.
Excuse me?
I figured I'd give the
firefighters a break.
I've put them through
enough already.
What'd you say your name was?
Currently I go by Adam Clay.
Trust me, if there
was a back entrance,
I would've used it.
I don't want to injure anyone
who's innocent and non-involved.
But it is what it is.
Somebody detain this guy!
Don't shoot! Don't shoot!
Oh, wow, if it isn't the fucking
golden goose himself.
Sir, I got Captain Caveman here
telling me to send
everyone home.
If we do that,
we're walking away
from a lot of money.
Mm. Put him on.
It's for you.
Why are you fucking
with my business?
Because Mr. Westwyld hired me
to kick some fucking
Beekeeper's ass.
Mr. Westwyld works for me,
which means that
you work for me.
Now, listen, that place
is the crown jewel
of my kingdom.
I'm not gonna let
some crash test dummy
with a fucking gun fuck it up.
Is that clear, Mr. Pettis?
Didn't this character
already burn
one of your centers
to the ground?
Well, you know, they
didn't have you,
and that's why.
So maybe you just
do your fucking job
and don't tell me how
to do mine, please.
- We got it?
- Copy that.
Fall out. Set up a
perimeter outside.
Let's go. Move!
Round of applause.
Let's say goodbye
to our good friends.
Bye-bye, Admiral. Go
join fucking Space Force.
You are beautiful.
Now get the fuck out!
Keep walking.
Bye-bye, dickhead.
What a bunch of jackoffs.
Yeah, we love you!
One time amnesty.
Whoever doesn't want
to die this evening,
can in an orderly
fashion leave now.
Uh, uh, uh. No fucking
way. It's not happening.
Anybody moves, you're fired.
- No bonus, vesting, two weeks.
- Come on, boys! Move, move!
Nada. Zero!
Are you fucking nuts?
Each one of these
pricks is worth
30 to 40 million
a year in profit.
So no one is shooting no guns.
Not a good day to drag
innocent people into this.
These assholes?
They're not innocent.
For either one of us
to close that distance,
some of them will get hurt.
Let's start with this
prick right here.
On me!
Take right!
Pettis, we got a man down.
Fire. Fire.
You know who you're working for?
None of my fucking business.
I'm just the guy they call
when there's a problem.
And you are our problem.
Goddamn right, I'm a problem.
Fire. Fire.
Dan, what the hell happened?
Any dead?
Not dead, but we got
our asses kicked.
- Our guy. What do we know?
- He's in the building.
I'm waiting more men to roll in.
I don't know what this guy is,
but nobody can do
what he's done.
He's just a Beekeeper.
Bad idea.
I'm not waiting.
- V, wait!
- Move!
Come on, Wiley, keep up.
Fuck.
We got him!
- You done?
- Reload.
Everybody out!
You're done.
We should take the stairs.
Smart.
Subject is in the hallway.
Command, report back.
Anybody on comm?
Please, please don't kill me.
I'm just a middle manager.
I never hurt nobody.
I'd respect you more
if you look people
in their eyes when
you steal from them.
Now, you're making
a lot of money here.
Tell me where it's all going.
I don't know, man.
I know you're the middle man.
- Who's above you?
- No. They'll kill me.
I'll torture you, then kill you.
Come on, guys. You got it.
Wiley, get your ass up here!
Yeah, well, I'm not an Olympian.
Make it stop.
You can make it stop.
You've stolen
hundreds of millions
from people who've done nothing
but work hard all their lives.
She was an educator, a mom.
Dedicated her whole
life to helping people.
Yesterday, she shot herself
because you took two million
from a charity she ran.
She was the only person
who ever took care of me.
Who and where, Mr. Anzalone?
- Tell me who and where.
- I can't.
Look, these people,
they're untouchable.
I can't...
No, please! Please!
Stop! I will! I will!
Let me show you.
I told you they
were untouchable.
Nobody's untouchable.
Sometimes when the
hive's out of balance...
you have to replace the queen.
Clay!
That man is directly responsible
for your mother's death.
I believe you.
But we have laws
for these things.
You have laws for these
things until they fail.
Then you have me.
Arrest him!
On your feet before I blow
your fucking head off.
I just been thrown through
a plate glass window.
Shut your fucking mouth!
Whoa. I have four kids.
I know. Three boys and a girl.
Wiley? You okay?
- Yeah. He went that way.
- You okay?
- Have you been hit?
- My wife thinks
I'm doing computer nerd shit.
Well, I won't tell
her if you don't.
- Have you been hit?
- No, I'm good, Mom.
Did you get him?
- Did you?
- No, he's tricky.
- Get up. You okay?
- Almost, but...
I guess that's just evidence.
- Can I borrow your gun?
- Yeah. Let's go.
- On me. On me. On me. On me.
- Clear!
I want interviews
with all of them.
We're going to talk.
Get him out of here.
Wiley.
Holy shit.
Do you mind if I ask you
a really boring question?
Do you actually prefer
the money or the power?
Mm.
That's deep.
Oh, I'm so sorry. Excuse me.
Oh, God. Uh...
Would you excuse me for
a moment? Come upstairs.
You said these guys were
the fucking best. Uh...
Why are they all dead?
You kicked the beehive
and now we have to
reap the whirlwind.
- Unless...
- Unless.
Unless, unless,
unless fucking what?
Maybe now is the time
to call your mother.
I'm paying you so
much fucking money
and your advice is
to call my mother?
He can't make his move on us
if we're in her
proximity, can he?
Her people.
You're a fuck.
- You're scared...
- I certainly am scared.
And you want to use my mother
as a human shield.
Just call her. Just
call her. Come on.
It's not a game now.
Oh, it's all a game.
Come on.
Yes, Derek. What do you want?
Hey, Mom. No, nothing.
I was just, you know,
thinking about you.
I miss you. I was hoping to
maybe see you this weekend.
I'm at the beach house.
You're welcome to
join if you behave.
I would love to. And, hey,
I actually was going to,
you know, get together
with some of my
tech homies and
stuff, if that's, uh,
if that's cool with you.
Fine. No drugs.
Give Kelly the details.
Love you. Have to go.
Derek's joining me this weekend.
Help me keep him sober.
Yes, ma'am. I
love babysitting.
Madame President, Funmi Lawal.
Hello. Good to meet you.
Sola Oyemade.
Sola, thank you so
much for coming.
Susan Aneno.
Thank you so much for
coming all this way.
Oli Ray-Imanuel.
- Oli, how good to meet you.
- Great to meet you, ma'am.
You don't have to
do this, you know?
Why not let Clay do his thing?
Your mom is dead
because of these people.
Wherever it's headed...
I swore an oath.
I can't stand by
and watch it happen.
Even if he's right?
Even if he's right.
Apologies. Damn
plane was delayed.
What have you got?
We think we have a sense of
Mr. Clay's true intentions.
He seems to be
following the money.
What money is that?
Usually it's from people
with no heirs, no family.
Nine Star United uses
data mining software
to identify these people and
then target their assets.
There's another
company involved, sir,
a company who is a vendor to
the intelligence community
and to the Justice Department.
In fact, we use this
company's software
in this very office
to identify financial fraud.
Are you going to tell me
the name of this company?
Danforth Enterprises.
With an annual revenue
of $10 billion,
founded and operated
by Jessica Danforth,
who recently stepped down
because she was sworn in
as President of
the United States.
She self-financed her campaign.
Yeah. None of that
money was clean.
Who else knows this?
Us three.
I have a really bad memory, sir.
Let's, uh, keep
the circle small,
until I can brief the director
and the attorney general.
Not a word of this to
anyone. Understood?
Yes, sir.
And, Mr. Clay, I
see his kill count
is steadily rising.
In a beehive, there is something
called a "queen slayer."
It's a bee that will rise
up and kill the queen
if she produces
defective offspring.
I thought we were sticking
to the known knowns.
Right. Yes. Not that
Beekeepers exist.
But Mr. Clay does
keep honey bees.
He admires their willingness
to sacrifice themselves
for the greater good.
Our concern is that Clay
believes that Derek Danforth
is the defective
offspring of a queen,
thereby Clay will strike
at the heart of the problem
and become a queen slayer.
Adam Clay's next victim is
Derek Danforth's mother?
President Danforth, sir.
You have a blank
check. Good luck.
Thank you.
Hey, whoa, whoa, whoa.
This is a private event.
I'm gonna need you to
turn around, go away.
Federal Bureau of
something or another.
We're good. We have
invites right here.
All right. You'll need
to excuse my partner.
He's recently concussed and
hasn't slept in two days.
We're on the access list.
We're good, boss.
Get the Secret Service
out of the house.
I don't want them here.
They're C team.
B team at best.
Uh, Mom's detail is
not going to like that.
Well, if Mom's detail
gets in the way
of what's coming for us,
they're dead men and so are we.
Tell them they can
stay in the kitchen.
Yes, sir.
He has a little
talent, doesn't he?
He's absolutely
fucking terrifying.
Yeah.
Good men, but clearly
not good enough.
- Hm.
- Fuck, bruh!
How'd you piss
this oak off, huh?
I...
- You're looking at me?
- Mm-hmm.
How is any of this my fault?
Wasn't your supersecret CIA
data mining software
supposed to,
I don't know, maybe filter out
un-fucking-stoppable
killing machines?
Don't you fuck
with me, young man!
Any other life,
you'd be in jail.
Hey, this is the
fucking Beekeeper!
Yeah, you know I
killed one once.
Oh, you see?
Yeah. Only 'cause I was lucky.
- And un-fucking-lucky.
- Oh, jeez.
Yeah, don't piss
your pants, bruh.
My team will be out shortly.
If anyone can knock
this guy's dick in
the dirt, it's them.
Ain't that right, money man?
Yeah.
I'm supposed to be at
a kids' birthday party
with my wife.
You are at a kids'
birthday party.
And I'm your work wife.
Madam President, you
look spectacular.
When the fuck are
you going to tell me
what's going on, Wallace?
Good. Go through.
Tell that guy to hurry up.
I want every manhole on
this street welded shut.
Six up.
Good to go.
Let's go. Let's go.
Come on. Move it up.
Put your head on a
swivel, gentlemen.
Go!
We got eyes on the second floor.
All right, you're
good. Coming through.
Oh.
Hey. When, uh, did you
get in? What a surprise.
You didn't hear the
giant Marine helicopter
land on the front lawn?
Ah, I guess not. Hm.
Is this, uh, nicotine
or a carnival ride?
Uh, I wouldn't
unless you want to go
talk with the machine elves.
Hey, you look fucking
great, by the way.
I mean, power, it just
looks so good on you.
Doing blow on your
father's desk.
God, how I wish
he was still alive
so I could kill him.
Stop picking your face.
Why does Wallace Westwyld
look nervous as a burning cat?
What have you done to the man?
Mm, I wouldn't know, Mother.
Well, he's there to protect you
if you'll let him.
You're a good looking kid.
You really are. You know that?
What does that mean?
It means that God doesn't
give with both hands.
Uh, okay. I love you too, Mom.
Hm.
Gotta go run the free world.
Don't burn it down.
Fucking fantastic!
Wiley, look.
Oh, shit.
Danforth looks like
she wants to throw up.
Look at her body
language. Bad vibes.
She got caught riding dirty.
What have we done?
Are you, uh, fucking with
crypto at all, right now?
It's gonna pop.
They're minting next week,
so just hit me up on Insta.
- Okay.
- I'll connect your wallet.
- May I borrow my son?
- Of course.
Speak to you a
moment in private?
Sorry.
Uh, who's this?
Jackson Prigg. He's
number two at the FBI.
Have a seat.
Uh, I'm cool. I'll stand.
What is this, like,
an ambush or something? This
feels weird. I don't like it.
No, you'll sit.
I'll sit.
Kelly, would you
give us a moment?
It's okay, ma'am.
I can take notes.
I need you to step outside.
The deputy director has
flagged his, uh, concerns
about some uncomfortable things
happening inside
the family company.
Like what?
Uncomfortable things about
the source of my campaign funds.
Sounds serious. What's up?
Deputy Director.
Mr. Danforth, are you familiar
with, uh, United Data Group?
United Data Group.
Yeah. Yeah, I, uh...
I invested in that.
I invest everywhere.
I mean, there's...
It's everywhere.
- It's very diverse.
- Uh-huh.
How about, uh, Nine Star United?
Yeah, that was, uh...
that's more of, like,
a consulting type role.
It's block chain issues.
And you probably...
I don't want to bore
you with all that.
What do you know about
a classified algorithmic
data mining software package
developed by the
intelligence community?
He's here.
All stations, target's in
the building. East wing.
Give me everything you got.
He's in the house!
Assault team, saddle up!
Let's move, boys!
Get a move on!
Let's move! Come on!
- Go! Come on. Move!
- Go! Go!
Break-break! Package
is in the house!
Level three, side four.
Blue over blue, you see
him, you fucking get him!
Hey! Put your
fucking hands up.
Now turn the fuck around.
- Fuck.
He's outside.
Target's outside.
Move! Move!
Let's get this fucking guy!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Easy, killer. You see him?
Negative.
- Clay!
- That's right.
That's right. Now,
on your knees!
On your knees!
Lace your fingers
behind your head.
Down on your knees now!
Do it now!
Beekeeper, huh?
God's right hand?
You aren't shit.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Hey, take a step back.
I'm putting this asshole's
brains on the lawn.
What are you doing?
He's not even armed.
Armed?
As long as this motherfucker's
breathing, he's armed.
You're not fucking
executing him.
Nice crowd you're rolling with.
Watch me.
V, what the fuck is going on?
To "bee" or not to "bee"?
Isn't that the bloody question?
I think I'll take
to "bee."
- Wiley?
- Yeah, you good?
- Yeah.
- Go.
Get off me!
He's fucking mine!
Talk to me, people.
I need news.
He's here!
Go! Go! All stations!
Take it easy. Take it easy.
Go with the flow.
Not clear. He's not clear.
Hang tight.
On me.
Get on the ground.
You understand you
did this, right?
You broke the rules.
You corrupted an imperfect
but functioning system.
I was just trying to get
you into office, Mom.
How else do you think
you got elected?
I was going to win with
or without your help.
We were already rich. Your
father built an empire.
Yeah. And you were
going to fucking
break it up into
pieces and sell it off.
Well, in the name
of public service
because I care and I want
to leave a better world.
Okay. Right.
Yeah, because you hate the fact
that being the president
is just like an
endless cocktail party.
You realize that you were behind
in 15 of 20 counties
you needed to win.
15 of 20 counties!
I taught CIA software
to hunt money
and not terrorists.
You didn't hear that.
You got elected because
of me, and you know that.
Yeah, I know it.
Everyone knows it.
Now I know where the
money came from...
and all the people you hurt.
Okay, whatever. It's
computer data, Mom.
Somebody in this family has
to have their fucking feet
on the ground to actually get
shit done. You understand that?
Mom, the wolves are at the
fucking door right now.
What are you going
to do to fix this?
Tell the truth.
The fucking...
What does that even mean?
What does that even mean,
tell the fucking truth?
You have an entire building
full of PR people
that are going to choose
the right way forward.
That guy who's coming to
kill us, that Beekeeper,
I'm telling him the truth
about what you did, Derek.
Then I'm telling
the entire nation.
And if it costs me everything,
well, so be it.
You fucking git!
Fuck!
You're just a man.
I know.
Thank you.
Jesus. Looks like a
tornado came through here.
What's your plan here, huh?
You're going to tell this
guy the fucking truth
and hope that he spares
you and kills me instead?
No, Derek, I'll
tell him the truth
because it's the truth.
It's gone far enough.
You've proved your point.
Beekeepers live for
the good of society.
I'm retired.
This is personal.
All the more reason to stop.
Go back. Live a quiet life.
Making honey for your neighbors.
That's all I wanted.
- My neighbor's dead.
- I know. I'm sorry.
But do you live
in the real world
or just protect it?
What does it matter to you
how presidents
come to be elected?
- Hm?
- It doesn't.
What does matter to you?
Right and wrong.
It's not fashionable.
I believe there's
good in the universe.
Yeah, well, we agree.
I mean, that's my view.
Until the Danforth
family bought you.
- Ah.
- You can stop pretending.
We wouldn't need Beekeepers
if it wasn't for men like you.
Don't do that.
Sir, you might
want to step back.
No.
- I don't want you to get hurt.
- I'm sorry. I can't do that.
Now, have a seat.
Nah, fuck the truth,
man. The truth...
- Wait. You put that down.
- No, Derek.
Comes out of your fucking...
Jesus Christ!
That's fucking real right there.
- Clay, no!
- Drop your weapon. Drop it!
You decide who you work for.
For the law
or for justice.
Fuck this.
Bye, Mom.
- Go! Go!
- Move. Move.
- Move it out. Out of the way.
- You're okay.
- I got you. I got you.
- No. No. I want my...
Clay!
Come with us right now!
- No! I want my... I want my...
- Back away. Back away.
No!
You need to come
with me. Come on.
- No!
- Move out. Move out.
- Give me your hand. Come on!
- No!
Goodbye, Adam Clay.
Keep eyes on! Let's go!
Modify by Blue-Bird™